<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Press on DillonBaird.io</title>
    <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Press on DillonBaird.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Baird Joins Inbrace team as Lead Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/inbrace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/inbrace/</guid>
      <description>Irvine, CA - Inbrace, a leading provider of orthodontic braces, has announced that software engineer Dillon Baird has joined the company as Lead Software Engineer.
With over 15 years of experience in the industry, Baird brings a wealth of knowledge and expertise to the team. He is a full-stack engineer with a specialty in design and user interface/user experience (UI/UX), and has worked on a variety of projects throughout his career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NautiWearz: The Nautical Fashion Line with a Sense of Fun</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/nautiwearz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/nautiwearz/</guid>
      <description>San Diego, CA – Local entrepreneur, Dillon Baird, is officially launching his nautical-themed fashion line NautiWearz that promises to bring style and comfort together. This unique line is inspired by Baird’s love for boating and aims to provide an unforgettable experience on the open water.
NautiWearz consists of a wide range of fashionable yet comfortable apparel that pays homage to the sea. From subtle nods to bold expressions, the clothing line is designed for those who want to make a statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Developer Recreates SpaceX&#39;s Crew Dragon UI</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/mutantdragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/mutantdragon/</guid>
      <description>San Diego, CA - Software developer Dillon Baird has successfully recreated the user interface (UI) of SpaceX&amp;rsquo;s Crew Dragon spacecraft in just 60 days. The project, called &amp;ldquo;MUTANTdragon,&amp;rdquo; was a personal challenge for Baird to improve his skills and potentially impress the team at SpaceX.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of SpaceX and the incredible work they are doing to advance space exploration,&amp;rdquo; said Baird. &amp;ldquo;I wanted to challenge myself and see if I could recreate their Crew Dragon UI in a short amount of time, using only my own skills and resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Waves In Tech Industry From A 65&#39; Motor Yacht</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/workfromyacht/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/workfromyacht/</guid>
      <description>Dillon Baird, a highly-skilled full-stack software engineer, UI/UX engineer, systems architect, graphic designer, security researcher, embedded systems engineer and consultant with over 15 years of experience has found a way to combine his two passions; technology and boating. He is able to work remotely while living aboard his 65&amp;rsquo; motor yacht (M/Y Antigua).
Baird is adept in all stages of advanced software development and highly effective design. Using multiple Starlink connections bonded together to achieve the internet speeds needed for remote software development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Baird Launches New Portfolio and Blog Website: DillonBaird.io</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>San Diego, CA - Local software engineer Dillon Baird has announced the launch of his new portfolio and blog website, showcasing his skills and experience in the tech industry.
With over 15 years of experience as a full-stack engineer, Baird has worked on a wide range of projects for clients in various industries. His portfolio website, located at https://DillonBaird.io , features a selection of his most notable projects, along with detailed descriptions and examples of his work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Baird Joins Lightstream as Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/lightstream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/lightstream/</guid>
      <description>San Diego, CA - Local software engineer Dillon Baird has announced that he has joined Lightstream, the online consumer lending platform owned by Suntrust bank, as a software engineer.
With over 12 years of experience in the tech industry, Baird brings a wealth of knowledge and expertise to the team at Lightstream. He is a full-stack engineer with a specialty in design and user interface/user experience (UI/UX), and has worked on a variety of projects throughout his career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GirlComps: Las Vegas Weekend Getaways Free for Women, Profitable for Venues</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/girlcomps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/girlcomps/</guid>
      <description>Las Vegas, NV - GirlComps, a Las Vegas-based company that provides free weekend trips to the city for women, is now a profitable venture. With successful collaborations with local venues, the company has been able to generate revenue while providing their female guests with complimentary tables and bottles. This mutually beneficial relationship has resulted in an influx of customers for the venues and an unforgettable experience for the women.
Dillon Baird, the CTO and creator of the platform that facilitates the coordination and automation of the trips, says “GirlComps is a win-win for both our clients and the venues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baird Productions Transforms Events and Software Development in the Coachella Valley</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/bairdproductions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/bairdproductions/</guid>
      <description>PALM SPRINGS, CA – Baird Productions has been making waves in the Coachella Valley for its work in event production and software development. The company, owned by Dillon Baird, has been in business for over six years, and has quickly become renowned for its ability to turn any event into an immersive experience.
When it comes to event production, Baird Productions has a long proven track record of creating remarkable experiences that transport their guests to another reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dillon Baird Takes 1st Place at National Speech and Debate Championship</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/debate_championship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/debate_championship/</guid>
      <description>San Antonio, TX - Middle school student Dillon Baird has won first place in the category of public forum debate at the Speech and Debate National Championship, held in San Antonio, TX.
Baird, a seventh grader at Desert Springs Middle School, competed against students from across the country in the public forum debate category. He won first place after delivering a series of compelling and well-argued speeches on a range of topics, including the role of government in healthcare, the ethics of genetically-modified foods, and the impact of technology on society.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
