<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SEA-NG on DillonBaird.io</title>
    <link>https://dillonbaird.io/projects/seang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SEA-NG on DillonBaird.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dillonbaird.io/projects/seang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design &amp; Implementation</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/projects/hold/sea-ng/parts/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/projects/hold/sea-ng/parts/1/</guid>
      <description>The first phase of our project - the research phase - was about gathering information, exploring possibilities, and identifying potential challenges. Now, in the design and implementation phase, we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on turning all that theoretical knowledge into tangible action. This is where we bring our Underwater Server Project, SEA-NG, to life.
Designing the Server Setup Our first task in this phase is to design the server setup that will be housed in our chosen pressure cooker pot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>overview</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/projects/hold/sea-ng/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/projects/hold/sea-ng/overview/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the beginning of an ambitious journey that brings the world of servers into a new, unexpected frontier - the ocean. This exploration is dubbed the &amp;ldquo;Underwater Server Project,&amp;rdquo; also known as &amp;ldquo;SEA-NG&amp;rdquo;. My mission? To challenge the conventional boundaries of data storage and processing. By merging the power of cutting-edge technology with the wild, unpredictable nature of the sea, I have a unique challenge on my hands.
At the heart of SEA-NG is a simple yet daunting question: Can I establish a reliable, efficient, and sustainable homelab at the bottom of the sea?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>research</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/projects/hold/sea-ng/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/projects/hold/sea-ng/research/</guid>
      <description>There are several crucial areas of research that have been identified as important to the success of this project. These areas cover a broad range of topics from cooling solutions to server configurations.
1. Cooling Solutions Effective cooling is a critical part of this project due to the intense heat generated by the server components. The underwater environment poses unique challenges and opportunities for cooling, and we&amp;rsquo;re exploring various innovative solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
