<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gear on DillonBaird.io</title>
    <link>https://dillonbaird.io/tags/gear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gear on DillonBaird.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dillonbaird.io/tags/gear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wireless External Storage With Native Plex Server</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/wd-my-passport-wireless-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/wd-my-passport-wireless-pro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When Apple launched the Vision Pro, it promised a revolution in spatial computing. But for those of us who love to consume and create media, the limited internal storage quickly became a glaring issue. Enter the &lt;strong&gt;WD My Passport Wireless Pro&lt;/strong&gt;, an unassuming device that has transformed my Vision Pro experience. It&amp;rsquo;s more than just an external drive; it&amp;rsquo;s a portable media server, a productivity hub, and a travel essential – all in one sleek package.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Developer&#39;s Journey With Spacial Computing</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/apple-vision-pro-developer-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/apple-vision-pro-developer-journey/</guid>
      <description>When I first slid on the Apple Vision Pro, I was bracing myself for another overhyped gadget. Instead, what I encountered was a transformative leap into the future of digital interaction. This wasn&amp;rsquo;t merely a high-tech toy; it was a tool that seamlessly wove itself into my daily coding rituals, shattering my preconceived limits of what technology could achieve. From that moment, I was hooked—immersed in a mixed reality that felt both groundbreaking and surprisingly intuitive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How E-Ink is Revolutionizing Our Digital World and Why You&#39;re Missing Out!</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/eink/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/eink/</guid>
      <description>Diving into a digital read can be a mixed bag. There you are, comfy in a quiet corner of your home, wrapped in your go-to blanket, ready for some undisturbed reading. You turn on your LCD tablet and, suddenly, it&amp;rsquo;s like you&amp;rsquo;re in a face-off with an overly bright flashlight. Then, switch the scene to reading outside on a sunny day. Instead of getting lost in your story, you&amp;rsquo;re wrestling with the sun&amp;rsquo;s glare bouncing off the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XReal Beam - A Mobile Software Engineer&#39;s Best Friend</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/xrealbeam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/xrealbeam/</guid>
      <description>As a software engineer, I find myself in a perpetual dance with screens, gracefully navigating between lines of code, debugging sessions, and virtual meetings that blur the lines between work and leisure. Whether I&amp;rsquo;m immersing myself in the complexities of programming or unwinding with my favorite YouTube channels, these screens have become an inseparable part of my daily routine, almost an extension of my digital existence. So, when whispers of the XReal Beam, a revolutionary device promising to redefine my screen experience, reached my eager ears, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but be drawn in by the intrigue and excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New 15&#34; MacBook Air M2 Has Ruined My Life - A Letter to Apple</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/dearapple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/dearapple/</guid>
      <description>In this light-hearted open letter to Apple, I recount the unexpected ways this mighty machine has disrupted my life of laid-back leisure. From its mind-boggling multitasking capabilities and lightning-fast speed to its dazzling Retina display, the MacBook Air M2 has transformed my digital existence. You see, this sleek and powerful creation from Apple has managed to turn my world upside down, and I can&amp;rsquo;t help but share my mixed feelings about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rediscovering the Power of Graphing Calculators</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/calculators-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/calculators-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>Picture this: A regular Thursday, my desk scattered with lines of code, my mind deep in the digital realm. Suddenly, a blast from the past interrupted my thoughts: what if I revisited the world of graphing calculators? Yes, those chunky, old-school gadgets we once deemed essential. As I delved deeper into this nostalgic quest, the lines between past and present began to blur. Intrigued? Let&amp;rsquo;s embark on this adventure and uncover why the HP Prime became my newest obsession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work From Anywhere using the XReal Air AR Glasses</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/xrealair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/xrealair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From ergonomic benefits to a virtual triple monitor setup, learn how you can make remote work a reality with the XReal Air AR glasses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restoring My Original iPod: A Nostalgic Dive into Digital Independence</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/ipod-refurb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/ipod-refurb/</guid>
      <description>In a world dominated by streaming and intangible media, the allure of tangible memories beckons. Dive into a journey of iPod nostalgia, innovation, and self-reliance as we resurrect the iconic iPod Video. This iPod restoration isn&amp;rsquo;t just technical; it&amp;rsquo;s a reflection on our evolving relationship with technology, music, and the tangible artifacts of our past. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a tech enthusiast, a music lover, or someone seeking digital independence, this article offers a blend of personal insights, a detailed tutorial, and a broader commentary on the significance of reclaiming our digital artifacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Sail For Success: Working Remotely From A Motor Yacht</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/workremote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/workremote/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving landscape of the digital age, remote work has taken on new dimensions, pushing the boundaries of what&amp;rsquo;s possible. Allow me to introduce myself - I&amp;rsquo;m Dillon Baird, a versatile professional who wears many hats, including full-stack software engineer, UI/UX expert, systems architect, graphic designer, security researcher, embedded systems engineer, consultant and more! But what sets my remote work experience apart from the norm is my unconventional office space: a 65&amp;rsquo; motor yacht named M/Y Antigua.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How A Tandy 1000 RSX Kickstarted My Career In Software Development</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/startingwithtandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/startingwithtandy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was 1996 and I was 5 years old in Silicon Valley, in the prime of computer surplus. I just pressed that big beautiful red power button on my newly acquired Tandy 1000 RSX someone just so happened to be throwing away down the street (a fairly regular occurrence with computer hardware at the time).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gear</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/gear/</guid>
      <description>Current Equipment The equipment I use today is leaps and bound from where I began; After many years attempting success on a very tight budget I&amp;rsquo;d gotten used to achieving what I needed to using the bare minimum hardware, but in recent years I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to &amp;ldquo;splurge&amp;rdquo; and treat myself to some newer gear, though still never &amp;rsquo;this years model&amp;rsquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m usually fairly flexible on where I&amp;rsquo;m working or what I&amp;rsquo;m working on, and can sometimes frequently change systems used through the week, but for the most part still always gravitate to the following gear:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
