<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on DillonBaird.io</title>
    <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on DillonBaird.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stats</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/stats/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brands</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/brands/</guid>
      <description>Throughout my professional journey, an inherent entrepreneurial spirit has been the driving force behind my ventures. Inspired by the thrill of building something from scratch, I&amp;rsquo;ve ventured into a multitude of business realms, learning and adapting along the way. From tech startups to clothing lines, each business has been a testament to my passion for creation and innovation.
Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the privilege of founding and managing a variety of small businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gear</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/gear/</guid>
      <description>Current Equipment The equipment I use today is leaps and bound from where I began; After many years attempting success on a very tight budget I&amp;rsquo;d gotten used to achieving what I needed to using the bare minimum hardware, but in recent years I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to &amp;ldquo;splurge&amp;rdquo; and treat myself to some newer gear, though still never &amp;rsquo;this years model&amp;rsquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m usually fairly flexible on where I&amp;rsquo;m working or what I&amp;rsquo;m working on, and can sometimes frequently change systems used through the week, but for the most part still always gravitate to the following gear:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/about/now/</guid>
      <description>Work Availability In the fast-paced and ever-evolving world of today, most of my time is absorbed by my full-time role and the ongoing maintenance of my various brands and side projects. The demand for my skills and expertise often outpaces the time I have available. As a result, it&amp;rsquo;s with regret that I currently find myself unable to take on any unsolicited projects. However, I understand the challenges of finding the right fit for your needs, and so I&amp;rsquo;m more than willing to provide referrals to professionals within my network who may be better able to assist you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
