<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>retrotech on DillonBaird.io</title>
    <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/tags/retrotech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in retrotech on DillonBaird.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/tags/retrotech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Born With The Web: Growing Up in a Digital Dawn</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/blog/first-clicks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/blog/first-clicks/</guid>
      <description>The World Wide Web and I have something in common: We both began our journey in 1991. While I&amp;rsquo;m just a dude in a vast world, and the internet has transformed global communication, it&amp;rsquo;s a humble thought to realize we&amp;rsquo;ve grown side by side. We might be seen as products of the same era, tracing parallel paths through time. As we stroll through the corridors of the past, prepare to journey through stories that resonate with nostalgia, laughter, tender moments, and of course, the unmistakable sound of dial-up—a symbol of our shared digital beginnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How E-Ink is Revolutionizing Our Digital World and Why You&#39;re Missing Out!</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/blog/eink/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/blog/eink/</guid>
      <description>Diving into a digital read can be a mixed bag. There you are, comfy in a quiet corner of your home, wrapped in your go-to blanket, ready for some undisturbed reading. You turn on your LCD tablet and, suddenly, it&amp;rsquo;s like you&amp;rsquo;re in a face-off with an overly bright flashlight. Then, switch the scene to reading outside on a sunny day. Instead of getting lost in your story, you&amp;rsquo;re wrestling with the sun&amp;rsquo;s glare bouncing off the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rediscovering the Power of Graphing Calculators</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/blog/calculators-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.github.io/public_DillonBaird.io/blog/calculators-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>Picture this: A regular Thursday, my desk scattered with lines of code, my mind deep in the digital realm. Suddenly, a blast from the past interrupted my thoughts: what if I revisited the world of graphing calculators? Yes, those chunky, old-school gadgets we once deemed essential. As I delved deeper into this nostalgic quest, the lines between past and present began to blur. Intrigued? Let&amp;rsquo;s embark on this adventure and uncover why the HP Prime became my newest obsession.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
