<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work From Home (WFH) on DillonBaird.io</title>
    <link>https://dillonbaird.io/tags/work-from-home-wfh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work From Home (WFH) on DillonBaird.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dillonbaird.io/tags/work-from-home-wfh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Developer&#39;s Journey With Spacial Computing</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/apple-vision-pro-developer-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/apple-vision-pro-developer-journey/</guid>
      <description>When I first slid on the Apple Vision Pro, I was bracing myself for another overhyped gadget. Instead, what I encountered was a transformative leap into the future of digital interaction. This wasn&amp;rsquo;t merely a high-tech toy; it was a tool that seamlessly wove itself into my daily coding rituals, shattering my preconceived limits of what technology could achieve. From that moment, I was hooked—immersed in a mixed reality that felt both groundbreaking and surprisingly intuitive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solo, Not Siloed: Navigating the AI Frontier in Development</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/solo-not-siloed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/solo-not-siloed/</guid>
      <description>The world of coding often paints a picture of intense late-night debugging sessions, relentless coding marathons, and the unparalleled joy of a successful deployment. My journey began in the cocoon of solitude, where every line of code was a tango between imagination and logic, often with only my trusty rubber duck as a confidant. However, as I honed my craft, I seamlessly transitioned into larger, team-based roles. Taking on the mantle of a Software Engineering Lead, I found my stride, collaborating with a dynamic team of professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Sail For Success: Working Remotely From A Motor Yacht</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/workremote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/workremote/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving landscape of the digital age, remote work has taken on new dimensions, pushing the boundaries of what&amp;rsquo;s possible. Allow me to introduce myself - I&amp;rsquo;m Dillon Baird, a versatile professional who wears many hats, including full-stack software engineer, UI/UX expert, systems architect, graphic designer, security researcher, embedded systems engineer, consultant and more! But what sets my remote work experience apart from the norm is my unconventional office space: a 65&amp;rsquo; motor yacht named M/Y Antigua.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Waves In Tech Industry From A 65&#39; Motor Yacht</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/workfromyacht/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/press/workfromyacht/</guid>
      <description>Dillon Baird, a highly-skilled full-stack software engineer, UI/UX engineer, systems architect, graphic designer, security researcher, embedded systems engineer and consultant with over 15 years of experience has found a way to combine his two passions; technology and boating. He is able to work remotely while living aboard his 65&amp;rsquo; motor yacht (M/Y Antigua).
Baird is adept in all stages of advanced software development and highly effective design. Using multiple Starlink connections bonded together to achieve the internet speeds needed for remote software development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gear</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/about/gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/about/gear/</guid>
      <description>Current Equipment The equipment I use today is leaps and bound from where I began; After many years attempting success on a very tight budget I&amp;rsquo;d gotten used to achieving what I needed to using the bare minimum hardware, but in recent years I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to &amp;ldquo;splurge&amp;rdquo; and treat myself to some newer gear, though still never &amp;rsquo;this years model&amp;rsquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m usually fairly flexible on where I&amp;rsquo;m working or what I&amp;rsquo;m working on, and can sometimes frequently change systems used through the week, but for the most part still always gravitate to the following gear:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
