<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apple on DillonBaird.io</title>
    <link>https://dillonbaird.io/tags/apple/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apple on DillonBaird.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dillonbaird.io/tags/apple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wireless External Storage With Native Plex Server</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/wd-my-passport-wireless-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/wd-my-passport-wireless-pro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When Apple launched the Vision Pro, it promised a revolution in spatial computing. But for those of us who love to consume and create media, the limited internal storage quickly became a glaring issue. Enter the &lt;strong&gt;WD My Passport Wireless Pro&lt;/strong&gt;, an unassuming device that has transformed my Vision Pro experience. It&amp;rsquo;s more than just an external drive; it&amp;rsquo;s a portable media server, a productivity hub, and a travel essential – all in one sleek package.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Developer&#39;s Journey With Spacial Computing</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/apple-vision-pro-developer-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/apple-vision-pro-developer-journey/</guid>
      <description>When I first slid on the Apple Vision Pro, I was bracing myself for another overhyped gadget. Instead, what I encountered was a transformative leap into the future of digital interaction. This wasn&amp;rsquo;t merely a high-tech toy; it was a tool that seamlessly wove itself into my daily coding rituals, shattering my preconceived limits of what technology could achieve. From that moment, I was hooked—immersed in a mixed reality that felt both groundbreaking and surprisingly intuitive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super73 RX &amp; Apple CarPlay: A Guide to E-Bike Modernization</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/carplay73/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/carplay73/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer with a two-decade-long passion for weaving technology into the fabric of everyday life. My latest endeavor? Integrating an Apple CarPlay display into my Super73 RX eBike. Ready to take your Super73 RX on a tech transformation journey? This guide is not just about adding a gadget; it&amp;rsquo;s about revolutionizing your ride with smart tech, blending the adventurous spirit of e-biking with the advanced features of modern technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New 15&#34; MacBook Air M2 Has Ruined My Life - A Letter to Apple</title>
      <link>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/dearapple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillonbaird.io/blog/dearapple/</guid>
      <description>In this light-hearted open letter to Apple, I recount the unexpected ways this mighty machine has disrupted my life of laid-back leisure. From its mind-boggling multitasking capabilities and lightning-fast speed to its dazzling Retina display, the MacBook Air M2 has transformed my digital existence. You see, this sleek and powerful creation from Apple has managed to turn my world upside down, and I can&amp;rsquo;t help but share my mixed feelings about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
